

# **Devashri Khandade**

Phone: + 91 77987 02228

Email: devashri.khandade@gmail.com

**LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/devashri-khandade/

Content Marketing Maven with extensive experience in developing, curating, and managing content across digital platforms. 5 years of experience in the Automotive sector - aligning content with brand voice and values, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure consistency, accuracy, and audience engagement and creating compelling content that resonates with target audiences.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Levi & Korsinsky**

Brand Communication Manager - May 2024 - Present

Brand and content strategy, influencer marketing, agency coordination, email marketing, lead management and more

Eminent Digitals October 2019 – May 2024

#### **Assistant Manager**

**Verticals** – Automotive, Hospitality, Healthcare, Lifestyle Electronics, F&B, Education, Online Freelance Portal, Group of Companies, e-commerce retail

- Strategizing content for marketing materials across multiple channels such as social media copies, ad copies, ad scripts, email marketing, as well as website/landing page content, OOH, print
- Monitored digital, industry, and competitive trends to identify potential business avenues and improve current content offerings
- Worked with one of India's leading brands to establish brand identity and maintain the brand voice and brand tone consistently across all marketing channels in both b2b and b2c set-ups
- Headed projects of digital and offline (360 degree) campaigns, integrated campaigns, complete with strategy, concepts, content, and designs
- Planning campaigns for new product launches and creating engaging yet captivating copies for the product as well as brand awareness
- Assisting the clients with all the requirements such as setting up brand guidelines, brand management, content for social media, SEO, Google ads services, PR, OOH, and more
- Well-versed in using AI tools such as ChatGPT to brainstorm ideas, and optimize workflow efficiency
- Developed and refined prompts for AI models, ensuring alignment with brand voice, target audience, and campaign objectives.
- Thoroughly proofread all the communication for correct tonality and placement to maintain a seamless and error-free execution

# **Amura Marketing Technologies**

October 2018 - June 2019

### Sr. Social Media Executive

Verticals – Real Estate

- Right from creating monthly planners (PowerPoint), calendars, CMS and creative copywriting to driving creative ideas and engaging campaigns exclusively every month
- 4 After a set planner filing content and design inputs, and coordinating with the respective teams to make sure the client expectations are met as per the brand guidelines and company goals
- Making sure that the content is curated as per the niche and potential audience and performing especially targeted paid activities for the same
- Monitoring the progress of the content and campaigns through Facebook ads manager, as well as other social tracking tools such as Sprout Social and Mention for ORM
- Generating relevant and detailed reports of the progress weekly and monthly to check the performance over short- and long-term goals
- Keeping up with the latest trending formats and updates on social media and other digital platforms Joining client meetings periodically to set goals and objectives with the client and the way forward

- ★ Keeping tabs on the competitor's performance
- 4 Additionally, planned singlehandedly and worked on special launch campaigns, such as new tower/project launch, involving both digital and traditional marketing efforts, client pitches, branding activities, written copies for several campaigns etc

Innoserv Digital November 2017 - July 2018

## Social Media Executive

Verticals – Education, Real-Estate

- Conceptualizing, planning & and implementing Digital marketing strategies, content strategies, setting up and optimizing suitable and result-oriented campaigns
- ♣ Monitoring trends via Social listening tools, applications, & channels
- Assisting clients in creating digital strategies, budget projections, and lead generation strategies on Google and Facebook helping them reach their objectives and beyond
- Working closely with the SEO, SEM, Design, & Development teams to carry out various Digital Marketing tasks, addressing client requirements and giving them remarkable client experiences
- ♣ Analysing, reviewing, and reporting to the clients on the effectiveness of DM strategies SEM, SEO, SMM, etc, to maximize ROI for the clients

Neuron Inc August 2015 - September 2016

### Social Media Manager

Verticals – AI & Machine Learning

- The Neuron projects include NLP, Deep Learning, & Neural Networks model-based marketing applications
- Recognizing the social channels that work best for the brand and its products
- ♣ Building online strategies for in-house social media, recognizing influencers in the field of machine learning and interacting with them through social channels for exposure
- Reaching out to potential customers and the AI community through striking content strategies based on current trends and the latest product developments
- Tracking and reporting all the developments and results through built-in social media analytics and maintaining communications throughout the company's social channels

#### **Education**

**Nagpur University** 

August 2009 – April 2015

Bachelor of Engineering
Electronics & Telecommunications

#### Skills

- Brand Identity & Positioning
- Copywriting
- Ad scripts
- Social Media Management
- ♣ Google Ad copies
- **4** Teamwork

#### **Written Features**

Featured writer in the Delhi Poetry Slam's 'Beetle Magazine' in the December 2023 issue.

## Relevant links:

## Social:

https://www.instagram.com/joy\_ebike/

https://www.instagram.com/quikshef retail/

https://www.instagram.com/bengalwizardsofficial/

https://www.facebook.com/oberoirealtyofficial

https://www.facebook.com/pridepurplegroup

Website:

https://www.joyebike.com/

https://quikshef.com/